なるほど　少しは「念」が 使えるようだが　やめときな。
What? Intruders?
あいつらは ただのコソ泥じゃ　ない。
Dispose of them. I'm busy right now.
殺しが 生活の一部みたいなもんだ。
Don't bother me with reports
I don't need to hear!
い…　いわば 殺しのプロだな　うん。
Carry on now.
うわ！
But having entered this palace, you must now die painful deaths. Your Majesty...
オークション会場を襲った 「幻影旅団」 マフィアの追跡部隊を
I needn't even strain my eyes to sense it.
たった１人で壊滅に追い込んだ ウボォーギン
This is a rare human.
その前に現れたのは マフィアの大幹部 十老頭達が差し向けた切り札 陰獣達であった
An appetizing treat.
まったく 歯応えのない奴らばっかりだぜ。
This is it... This is the flavor I sought!
ウボォー！ あぁ？
I feel it.
来たよ！
I feel it! I feel it!
ヘヘ…。
Nyow I understand...
おいおい 余計な手出しするんじゃねえぞ。
This is the King's power.
俺は　まだ全然 暴れ足りねえんだからよ。
He can take aura from rare humans he consumes.
やれやれ…。 ここは　ウボォーに任せて フェイタンも　ひと勝負　どう？
In other words, the more he eats, the stronger he will grow.
あいつ…　１人で　陰獣達の 相手をしようってのか？
Hmm? Who are you people? Guards!
「陰獣」か。
Insolent thugs!
競売品を　どこにやった？
Do you know who I am? A supreme leader of this era, a king among kings...
警備と客を　どうした？
I am Masador Diego!
殺した！　競売品は？
Why does that scum claim to be the king?
答えねえと…。
In the human world, it is a common phenomenon.
うっ…。
end up in positions of power due
to bloodline or connections. That defies all logic...
効いたぜ。
In the hands of an incompetent,
power brings nothing but ruin.
ギャ！
This could only be the work of imbeciles.
フッ。
We must provide proper guidance.
ん？
However, they serve as quality meat, and they are a self-renewing resource.
フフフ…　もう逃げられねえぜ。
The non-rare humans can be
used to feed our soldiers.
さぁ　選びな。 下で　俺に殺されるか
I shall use my godly power
to deal divine punishment!
上で　他の３人に殺されるか。
Leave at once—
バカが…。
I can use it to control other humans.
ウボォーも本気だね。 ４。
These humans are idiots.
逃げられねえのは
Think as hard as those weak
brains of yours can manage.
てめぇだ！
Have you ever spared a pig or a cow
あぁ…。 し…　信じられねえ！
After being defeated by Knuckle
and Shoot, Gon and Killua return to the inn where Palm waits.
「クモ」…。
What?!
あ…。 気の毒に　跡形もねえぜ。
You promised to take me to NGL...
ウボォーの 「ビッグバンインパクト」は。
You said you'd swallow a thousand needles
ぶっちゃけ 「念」を込めただけの
if you broke that promise.
右ストレートなんだけどね。
Uh-huh, I'm sorry.
８。 ９。
I don't want an apology...
１０っと。 さぁ　次は　誰が死ぬ？
But there's no point in having you
swallow a thousand needles. Yeah.
「幻影旅団」か…。
So what can I do to make up for it?
ペッ　死ぬのは　てめぇだよ！ バカ野郎が。
You must... do any one thing I say.
いいねぇ 命知らずで好きだぜ　お前ら。
Hey! Right now, do you know how Gon feels— Okay, I agree!
だが　死ね！
Go out with me.
お？ 俺は　体毛を自在に操り 強靭な針にも 変えることができるな　うん。
Go out with me... Eh? Okay. Huh?
すごいパンチだが 体まで届かなけりゃ 意味ないな　うん。
Do you have any idea what you're doing?! Yeah, but I did say I'd do anything.
ペッ！
And you have no problem
playing dirty like this?!
体毛や歯で　鋼鉄を誇る ウボォーギンの肉を裂くとは…。
This is none of your business. It's our problem.
かなり鍛えられた念能力者だ やるよ　あいつら。
It's up to the two of us.
ダウト！ すみません。
You should stay away from her, Gon.
ゲッ！
Don't interrupt us!
手伝おうか？　ウボォー！
This is something the two
of us must decide alone.
余計なお世話だ！
You just want an excuse to say that!
クソっ　この！
Just be quiet.
うん　無理　無理。
We're going out now...
数千本の髪が絡みついたら もう外せないな　うん。
There's somewhere I really want to go.
なら　てめぇごと 拳として使ってやるぜ！
Oh, sorry. I can't go out today. Eh? Today, I have to train with Killua.
ん？
You can train with us, Palm!
自在に操れるから
Huh?
部分的に軟らかくすることも 簡単だな　うん　うん。
What are you talking about? Didn't you say we'd go out?
ペッ！　筋肉バカが　手玉だぜ！ ほざけ！
Uh-huh. Then, why is he tagging along? And why would we train?
おっ？
This will be a date... Our first date!
タフな野郎だ ようやく効いて来たか。
The first date for us!
牙に仕込んだ神経毒は　超即効で 体の自由を奪うはずなんだがな。
The! First! Date! But it isn't a date.
てめぇ…。
Huh?!
首から上は無事だから 痛みも恐怖も自覚できる。
We can have a proper date later.
まぁ　楽しんでくれ。
Since it's our first date, like you said.
致死量の猛毒にすれば 勝負は決まってたのに。
Wow... The word "date" keeps popping up.
拷問好きなんだろ　きっと。
And I need time to prepare for it, too.
グシュシュシュ…。
Prepare? Prepare for what?
俺は体内に　大小無数の ヒルを飼っている。
That's... a secret. You get to find out tomorrow.
あんたには 傷口から体内に潜り込み
Oh...
膀胱に卵を産みつける
In that case, it's fine.
マダライトヒルを プレゼントしよう。 気持悪ぃな　てめぇ！
Really... If you'd explained first,
I wouldn't have been so angry.
グシュシュシュ…。
Sorry about that.
大抵の人間は
But I wanted to keep it secret, to surprise you!
卵からかえった何億という ヒルの赤ん坊が出る時
You wanted to surprise me? Gosh...
その激痛で　暴れ死ぬ。 ゲヘヘ…！
Let's meet tomorrow, at 10 AM,
in front of the bulletin board. I'll be there!
ん　まずいな。
Gon, you're amazing! Huh? What do you mean?
げてものは　美味と 相場が決まってるんだがな。
Well, listening to you talk to Palm,
you seemed used to this stuff.
かむのは おめぇの専売特許じゃねえぞ。
I was wondering...
フフ！ あ…。
Hmm?
てめぇら倒すのに 首から上が動けば　十分だ。
Have you been on a date before? Sure, I have. Well, most of them were with Mito-san.
負ける。
Oh, some of the fishing boats
陰獣達は…　負ける。
that stopped at Whale Island were full of women, some of whom only liked younger men...
負ける。
Women like that were called fanatics.
陰獣達は…　負ける。
Haven't you ever been on a date, Killua? No! Of course not...
俺達を倒すだと？　ヘッ。
I spent all my time training as an assassin.
この距離じゃ　さっきみてぇに
And ever since I quit, I've been with you. Oh, yeah.
俺をかみちぎることは できねえぜ。 フフフ。
Right! And I really don't want that to change...
あっ！ あぁ…　あ…。
We've located and secured Kite. Really? Kite's okay?
あぁ…！ 俺にも来るか でも無駄なんだな
I believe that Kite's being controlled by the enemy.
体毛針で　どんな弾でも はじき返せるな　うん… フン！
So I wouldn't say that he's okay.
ん!?
That's fine. There must be a way to bring him back!
ウオ!!
All right, it'll take three days to get back, so watch out for any soldier ants.
うっ…。
Yes!
音で「陰獣」　倒すとは…。
Wow!
奴ら…　半端ねえ…。
Look over here!
あ…。
I've found a new feeding ground.
このバカ野郎！ やるならやるって言え！
There we go.
俺達の鼓膜まで破る気か。
What's that for?
悪ぃ　悪ぃ！
It's a present for Palm.
でも　言ったら 奴らにバレるじゃねえか。
Are you sure about this?
それに　音が　そっちに届く前に 耳をふさぐことぐらい
If you hand that to her, won't she freak out?
お前らなら朝飯前だろ？
If I just hand it to her, probably...
確かにね。 なっ！
Whatever... Let's get back to town. Yeah.
決まっているだろう 奴を捕らえる。 無理だ！　見ただろう　奴の能力を 死に急ぐようなものだ！
If we encounter soldier ants
here, in the mountains, we'll be in serious trouble.
クラピカ!! 関係ない。
Likewise, if we stay in town, the risk of
encountering ants looking for humans is high.
何て　すさまじい 怒りと憎しみの音…
After all, Gon can't currently use his Nen...
完全に我を忘れている
So I must protect him. Even if it means sacrificing everything else!
なっ！
Let's hurry.
『野の花』 リラックスに最適の曲よ。
Today, around noon, an unidentified creature killed
seven people in Pata City.
皆さん　落ち着いたかしら？
The creature also injured multiple police
officers who had rushed to the scene, before escaping into the Miera Mountains.
まずは冷静になって 作戦を立てましょ。 あ…　ああ。
According to police testimony, the creature moved at speeds exceeding
two hundred kilometers per hour.
「陰獣」を倒した奴以外に どんな能力があるのか。
Before leaving, it said, "I'll return
tomorrow. Bring faster humans,"
センリツ。 ん？
which means it could be a new
species of Magical Beast. An evacuation has been ordered
for all area residents.
礼を言う　頭は冷えた。
Pata City and the Miera Mountains...
だが　奴らは捕らえる。 え？
Another city lies between us, with the Miera Mountains on the opposite side.
リーダー。 ん？
We should be okay...
勝算は　ある。 何だと？ やらせてくれ。
The government has requested that
the Hunter Association capture it, and the Association has accepted. Next, we have the weather.
勝算が　あると言うのだな？ もちろんだ。
Tomorrow, we're both on our own.
分かった。
Yeah, I'll be training all day in the gym.
すぐに　ここを動けるよう 車を回しておいてくれ。 あ…　ああ。
Yeah, right.
俺の体の中から 毒とヒルを吸い出してくれ。
Gon-kun, over here.
お前の掃除機ならできるだろ？
Hmm?
丸一日かけて 人畜の膀胱に　たどり着き
I didn't recognize you! Who are you?!
卵を産むと死ぬんです。
Do I look strange?
ほぉ　それで？
Nope, you look really pretty!
卵は　すぐに孵化して 尿とともに排出されますが
Wait, stop it... You're too loud.
その時の痛みは死に値します。
You're embarrassing me...
おい　おい　おい！ 冗談じゃねえぜ！
What? I'm just telling the truth.
安定したアンモニア濃度が 必要であり
That's enough. Let's go. Quickly.
うん！
Damn...
誰か街へ行って ビールを　たくさん取って来てよ。
What am I doing?
俺が行く。 キンキンに冷えたやつ　頼むぜ！
Now I look like the stalker!
ぜいたく言うな！
No, don't let it get to me. I have to protect Gon!
ギョギョギョ。 よし 早いとこ吸い出してくれや。
There's no telling when
the enemy will show up.
新手の「陰獣」か…。
Something's there.
ウボォーは　毒で身体が動かねえし ヒルも体内に入ったままだ。 仕方ない　助けに行くか。
This aura is probably from a soldier ant. It isn't that close, but it isn't that far, either.
やれやれ　世話　焼けるね。
There are faint aura traces around. Did it already pass through the area?
糸の気配は 「隠」で消してあるから 「凝」で見破られるか 針に気づかれない限り
Or were they brought here by the wind? Either way, there's a high
risk our paths will cross!
どこまででも追跡できる。
Should I warn them?
よし　悟られる前に追いつこう。 フッ。
We're here. Eh?
ヘッ！ 追跡のほうが楽しそうなのによ。
It's beautiful...
ハハハ…　行くぞ！
No, there's no point in telling them.
そう…　「クモ」だ…。
Gon can't use his Nen.
残り… 全員で　かからねえと…
If he gets upset about Kite and flies
off the handle with rage, he's finished.
危ない…　ぜ…。
Knowing Palm, she'll definitely
go nuts if I interrupt her date.
ヘイ　運転手さんよ こんな鎖で 俺を捕らえたつもりかよ。
I'll take care of this myself!
同等に近い力を この　ちっぽけな鎖に 込めてやがるってのか！
Oh, I thought I smelled a human... That's...
「チェーンジェイル」
You're one of those kids from before!
これは　お前達 「クモ」にしか使わない力
Looks like your luck's run out.
「幻影旅団」を捕らえ その自由を奪う
You're about to get a taste of hell.
そのためだけに使うと 誓った力
But it won't last forever.
もしも　「クモ」ではない者に この力を使ってしまった場合…
I moved upwind to catch his attention and draw him away from them. I've done what I had to.
即座に　私自身が 命を失うよう条件をつけた
But... Where's the other kid? Once you tell me his location,
I'll give you an easy death.
「制約と誓約」
Well, he can't be that far away...
これは覚悟の証し！
He's your buddy, right?
危ないわよ　クラピカ！ リスクはバネ！ 前　前！
Well, it doesn't matter if you talk or not.
制約と覚悟が大きいほど 「念」は強く働く！
I'll just walk around making lots of noise
and swinging your severed head.
一族の敵　「幻影旅団」の １人を捕らえたクラピカ
Isn't that how humans are? He's right.
命のリスクと覚悟を背負った 激しい戦いの幕が開く
I have to defeat him, or it's all over!